let leadershipDiagram = () => {
  return [{
		"Subject": "Leadership Management Chart",
		"Topic": "Wall Walks",
		"Question": "What is a constraint?",
		"Answers": [
			"The gate with the lowest throughput.",
			"The most important gate in the machine.",
			"The amount of time it takes to complete a product.",
			"A rule that must be upheld in order to maintain safety."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["The gate with the lowest throughput."],
		"Justifications": [
			"Yes! A gate with the lowest throughput constrains the system capacity.",
			"No! A gate with the lowest throughput constrains the system capacity.",
			"No! A gate with the lowest throughput constrains the system capacity.",
			"No! A gate with the lowest throughput constrains the system capacity."
		]
  },
   {
		"Subject": "Leadership Management Chart",
		"Topic": "Wall Walks",
		"Question": "What is a Wall Walk?",
		"Answers": [
			"A visual representation of a single process.",
			"A method of analyzing a value stream map to determine value.",
			"An established frequent review of WIP.",
			"A recurring, process-focused review to understand the machine."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["A recurring, process-focused review to understand the machine."],
		"Justifications": [
			"No",
			"no",
			"No",
			"yes"
		]
  },
  {
		"Subject": "Leadership Management Chart",
		"Topic": "Art of the Possible",
		"Question": "What is takt time?",
		"Answers": [
			"The time it takes to plan before production begins.",
			"The time spent selling your product to a customer.",
			"How often a single unit must be produced from a machine.",
			"The hours in a day that can be used for manufacturing."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["How often a single unit must be produced from a machine."],
		"Justifications": [
			"No",
			"no",
			"Yes",
			"no"
		]
  }];
}


let littlesLaw = () => {
	return [{
		"Subject": "Little's Law",
		"Topic": "Wall Walks",
		"Question": "What is a constraint?",
		"Answers": [
			"The gate with the lowest throughput.",
			"The most important gate in the machine.",
			"The amount of time it takes to complete a product.",
			"A rule that must be upheld in order to maintain safety."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["The gate with the lowest throughput."],
		"Justifications": [
			"Yes! A gate with the lowest throughput constrains the system capacity.",
			"No! A gate with the lowest throughput constrains the system capacity.",
			"No! A gate with the lowest throughput constrains the system capacity.",
			"No! A gate with the lowest throughput constrains the system capacity."
		]
  },
   {
		"Subject": "Little's Law",
		"Topic": "Wall Walks",
		"Question": "What is a Wall Walk?",
		"Answers": [
			"A visual representation of a single process.",
			"A method of analyzing a value stream map to determine value.",
			"An established frequent review of WIP.",
			"A recurring, process-focused review to understand the machine."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["A recurring, process-focused review to understand the machine."],
		"Justifications": [
			"No",
			"no",
			"No",
			"yes"
		]
  },
  {
		"Subject": "Little's Law",
		"Topic": "Art of the Possible",
		"Question": "What is takt time?",
		"Answers": [
			"The time it takes to plan before production begins.",
			"The time spent selling your product to a customer.",
			"How often a single unit must be produced from a machine.",
			"The hours in a day that can be used for manufacturing."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["How often a single unit must be produced from a machine."],
		"Justifications": [
			"No",
			"no",
			"Yes",
			"no"
		]
  }, 
  {
		"Subject": "Little's Law",
		"Topic": "Wall Walks",
		"Question": "What is a Wall Walk?",
		"Answers": [
			"A visual representation of a single process.",
			"A method of analyzing a value stream map to determine value.",
			"An established frequent review of WIP.",
			"A recurring, process-focused review to understand the machine."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["A recurring, process-focused review to understand the machine."],
		"Justifications": [
			"No",
			"no",
			"Yes",
			"no"
		]
  }, 
  {
		"Subject": "Little's Law",
		"Topic": "Art of the Possible",
		"Question": "What is the equation for evaluating Takt Time?",
		"Answers": [
			"Takt Time = total time available",
			"Takt Time = total time / number of products to be produced",
			"Takt Time = products to be produced / production days",
			"Takt Time = production days * products to be produced"
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["Takt Time = total time / number of products to be produced"],
		"Justifications": [
			"No",
			"no",
			"Yes",
			"no"
		]
  }, 
  {
		"Subject": "Little's Law",
		"Topic": "The Process Machine",
		"Question": "Are queued assets good or bad for the machine? Why?",
		"Answers": [
			"Good: it identifies a constraint",
			"Bad: because there is a constraint in the machine",
			"Bad: queue is waste",
			"Both: It does create waste, but it also identifies a constraint"
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["Both: It does create waste, but it also identifies a constraint"],
		"Justifications": [
			"No",
			"no",
			"Yes",
			"no"
		]
	}];
}  

let radiatorChart = () => {
  return [{
		"Subject": "Radiator Chart",
		"Topic": "Wall Walks",
		"Question": "What is a constraint?",
		"Answers": [
			"The gate with the lowest throughput.",
			"The most important gate in the machine.",
			"The amount of time it takes to complete a product.",
			"A rule that must be upheld in order to maintain safety."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["The gate with the lowest throughput."],
		"Justifications": [
			"Yes! A gate with the lowest throughput constrains the system capacity.",
			"No! A gate with the lowest throughput constrains the system capacity.",
			"No! A gate with the lowest throughput constrains the system capacity.",
			"No! A gate with the lowest throughput constrains the system capacity."
		]
  },
   {
		"Subject": "Radiator Chart",
		"Topic": "Wall Walks",
		"Question": "What is a Wall Walk?",
		"Answers": [
			"A visual representation of a single process.",
			"A method of analyzing a value stream map to determine value.",
			"An established frequent review of WIP.",
			"A recurring, process-focused review to understand the machine."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["A recurring, process-focused review to understand the machine."],
		"Justifications": [
			"No",
			"no",
			"No",
			"yes"
		]
  },
  {
		"Subject": "Radiator Chart",
		"Topic": "Art of the Possible",
		"Question": "What is takt time?",
		"Answers": [
			"The time it takes to plan before production begins.",
			"The time spent selling your product to a customer.",
			"How often a single unit must be produced from a machine.",
			"The hours in a day that can be used for manufacturing."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["How often a single unit must be produced from a machine."],
		"Justifications": [
			"No",
			"no",
			"Yes",
			"no"
		]
  }];
}
let criticalPath = () => {
  return [{
		"Subject": "Critical Path",
		"Topic": "Critical Path",
		"Question": "What is Critical Path?",
		"Answers": [
			"A set list of critical activities that lead to deliverable management.",
			"The path on the project where the project manager realizes he needs more management oversight.",
			"The set of activities, if not completed on time will extend the end date of the project.",
			"Extra float in the project that allows the end date to remain the same."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["A set list of critical activities that lead to deliverable management."],
		"Justifications": [
			"",
			"",
			"",
			""
		]
  },
   {
		"Subject": "Critical Path",
		"Topic": "Critical Path",
		"Question": "What is fast tracking?",
		"Answers": [
			"A high speed train.",
			"A way to decrease critical path by performing activities in series.",
			"A way to decrease critical path by performing activities in parallel.",
			"A way to increase critical path."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["A way to decrease critical path by performing activities in parallel."],
		"Justifications": [
			"",
			"",
			"",
			""
		]
  },
  {
		"Subject": "Critical Path",
		"Topic": "Critical Path",
		"Question": "Of these two project paths, which one is the critical path? Path 1 duration is 17 weeks, Path 2 duration is 144 days, Path 3 is 19 weeks, Path 4 is 133 days.",
		"Answers": [
			"Path 1",
			"Path 2",
			"Path 3",
			"Path 4"
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["Path 2"],
		"Justifications": [
			"",
			"Path 1 is 17 weeks or 119 days; Path 3 Is 19 weeks or 133 days",
			"",
			""
		]
  },
  {
		"Subject": "Critical Path",
		"Topic": "Critical Path",
		"Question": "You are the project manager for your organization and are creating the project schedule.  You know that a project schedule is composed of all the following components except for which one?",
		"Answers": [
			"The network of all the tasks within the project.",
			"The assignment of resources.",
			"The budget for the project.",
			"The reflection of the WBS."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["The budget for the project."],
		"Justifications": [
			"",
			"",
			"",
			""
		]
  },
  {
		"Subject": "Critical Path",
		"Topic": "Critical Path",
		"Question": "You are the project manager for your organization, and you are creating the project management plan.  You are reviewing the project scope baseline with your team so that theyâ€™ll understand the requirements and direction of the project.  Which of the following is the correct definition of the project scope baseline?",
		"Answers": [
			"It is all the work, and only the required work, to meet the project objectives",
			"It is the combination of the project scope statement, the WBS, and the WBS dictionary.",
			"It is the combination of the project requirements, the project scope, and the WBS.",
			"It is the consideration of the project requirements, assumptions, and constraints that affect the project planning."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["It is the combination of the project scope statement, the WBS, and the WBS dictionary."],
		"Justifications": [
			"",
			"",
			"",
			""
		]
  },
  {
		"Subject": "Critical Path",
		"Topic": "Critical Path",
		"Question": "You and the team have identified the critical path and are now reviewing the available float in your project network diagram.  All of the following statements about float are incorrect except for which one?",
		"Answers": [
			"Every project will have float.",
			"Only complex projects will have float.",
			"Float is the amount of time an activity can be delayed without increasing the project costs.",
			"Float is the amount of time an activity can be delayed without causing the project to be late."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["Float is the amount of time an activity can be delayed without causing the project to be late."],
		"Justifications": [
			"",
			"",
			"",
			""
		]
  },
  {
		"Subject": "Critical Path",
		"Topic": "Critical Path",
		"Question": "What two project planning elements are required to be able to calculate the critical path on a project?",
		"Answers": [
			"Project budget and Responsibility Matrix.",
			"WBS and project end date.",
			"Network diagram and task duration estimates.",
			"Donâ€™t know."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["Network diagram and task duration estimates."],
		"Justifications": [
			"",
			"",
			"",
			""
		]
  }];
}

let questionFunctionNames = [leadershipDiagram, littlesLaw, radiatorChart, criticalPath];
